I'm going to read exactly what this book says. You guys might find it interesting.
A long time ago, way before you were born, a group of white people made up an
idea called race. They sorted people by skin color and said that white people
were better, smarter, prettier, and they deserved more than everybody else. This
would be taught if we socialize our pre-k system. This would be taught...
Do you disagree with the findings in the book?
A thousand percent. How about we teach Jesus loves me? How about this? In teaching
Jesus loves little children, the letters go red and yellow, black and white, they're
all precious in our sight. Now which one would you think would be better? I'll
ask everybody on the panel. Which is better to teach? This? That is a story that was
made up to teach our kids. Three-year-olds who have no idea what race is. Now
all of a sudden it's being taught that white people said this as a truth. Someone
pointed at me that this being a truth, that white people developed race. First, it is
important that we teach Jesus. And Jesus is what we teach. But the reality is...
Do you think this is the right thing? Could you answer the question please? I don't want
reality. I'm asking the question which one is better. That is exactly, that's exactly what
it is. Got it on tape. Misspoke.